softwex.com 2019-02-15

# Softwex: Privacy Policy

**Softwex.com Privacy Policy**

**Softwex for Information Technology Ltd ("we") are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.**

### 1\. Information we may collect from you

**1.1** We may collect and process the following data about you:

**1.1.1** information that you provide by filling in forms on our website http://softwex.com (our "site"). This includes information provided at the time of registering an account, purchasing services from us or requesting further services. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our site or the services you have purchased;

**1.1.2** if you contact us letter or email, we may keep a record of that correspondence;

**1.1.3** if you contact us by telephone, we may record our telephone conversation for training purposes and, if you are asking us to provide you with the use of a dedicated hosting server, for the purposes of proving your request;

**1.1.4** we may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them;

**1.1.5** details of transactions you carry out through our site and of the fulfillment and administration of your orders; and

**1.1.6** details of your visits to our site including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data, whether this is required for our own billing purposes or otherwise and the resources that you access and use.

### 2\. IP addresses and cookies

**2.1** We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users' browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.

**2.2** For the same reason, we may obtain information about your general Internet usage by using a cookie file which is stored on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer's hard drive. They help us to improve our site and to deliver a better and more personalized service. They enable us:

**2.2.1** to estimate our audience size and usage pattern;

**2.2.2** to store information about your preferences, and so allow us to customize our site according to your individual interests;

**2.2.3** to speed up your searches; and

**2.2.4** to recognize you when you return to our site.

**2.3** You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our site. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log on to our site.

### 3\. Uses made of the information

**3.1** We use information held about you in the following ways:

**3.1.1** to ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer;

**3.1.2** to provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes;

**3.1.3** to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us;

**3.1.4** to allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so;

**3.1.5** to notify you about changes to our service.

**3.2** If you have placed an order for our services, we will use the information we hold to send you our regular newsletter. This newsletter is our primary method of communicating with you and will inform you of changes to our site, notify you of planned outages and updates to our services, and keep you informed about our services generally. By placing an order for our services, you consent to us using the information we hold about you in this way.

**3.3** If you are an existing customer, we will only contact you by electronic means (e-mail or SMS) with information about goods and services similar to those which were the subject of a previous sale to you.

#### 4\. Disclosure of your information

**4.1** We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries.

**4.2** We may disclose your personal information to third parties:

**4.2.1** in the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets; or

### 5\. Disclosure of your information

**5.1** Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

### 6\. Changes to our privacy policy

**6.1** Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail.

### 7\. Contact

**8.1** Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to Softwex for Information Technology Ltd, via the email address support@softwex.com
